<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Integrates on Mattermost Developers</title>
    <link>https://developers.mattermost.com/integrate/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Integrates on Mattermost Developers</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 20 Aug 2017 12:33:36 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://developers.mattermost.com/integrate/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://developers.mattermost.com/integrate/apps/app-lifecycle/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://developers.mattermost.com/integrate/apps/app-lifecycle/</guid>
      <description>App Lifecycle App Bundle An app bundle is a convenient way to deliver an app to the Mattermost ecosystem. It provides a way to organize code and resources needed for an app to run. An app bundle is created by the developer of the app. Mattermost uses app bundles to provision and install/uninstall apps.
The app bundle contains a manifest.json file, a static/ folder (optional), and one or several lambda function bundles.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://developers.mattermost.com/integrate/apps/using-mattermost-api/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://developers.mattermost.com/integrate/apps/using-mattermost-api/</guid>
      <description>Using Mattermost APIs Authentication and Permissions OAuth2 is not yet implemented, for now session tokens are passed in as ActingUserAccessToken
An app can use the Mattermost server REST API, as well as new &amp;ldquo;App Services&amp;rdquo; APIs offered specifically to Mattermost Apps. An app authenticates its requests to Mattermost by providing access tokens, usually Bot Access token, or user&amp;rsquo;s OAuth2 access token. Each call request sent to the app includes Mattermost site URL, and optionally one or more access tokens the app can use.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://developers.mattermost.com/integrate/apps/using-third-party-api/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://developers.mattermost.com/integrate/apps/using-third-party-api/</guid>
      <description>Using 3rd party APIs Mattermost Apps framework provides services for using remote (3rd party) OAuth2 HTTP APIs, and receiving authenticated webhook notifications from remote systems. There are 2 examples here to illustrate the OAuth2 and webhook support.
Hello OAuth2! Here is an example of an HTTP App (source), written in Go and runnable on http://localhost:8080.
 It contains a manifest.json, declares itself an HTTP application, requests permissions and binds itself to locations in the Mattermost UI.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>